facerepo.com 2015-10-19

# Privacy | FaceRepo

This privacy policy sets out how FaceRepo.com uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website.

FaceRepo.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

FaceRepo.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from October 5th, 2014. 

### What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * site user name
  * email address
  * site password

### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information (when registering for an account) to provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * We will use your email address and password to authenticate you when logging in.
  * We will use your user name when showing site users content you've contributed.
  * We will never sell your information.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Controlling your personal information

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law. 

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email [tickets@facerepo.uservoice.com](mailto:tickets@facerepo.uservoice.com).

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. 

### Advertisements on this site

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to this site.
  * Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users of this site based on visits to this site and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Google may also collect device-specific information, location information and other information stored on, accessed on, or collected from your device in connection with its services.
  * You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Google's ads settings page](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). You can also opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://aboutads.info/). 
  * Third party vendors may advertise on this site via Google's ad network. A list of approved third party advertisers can be found on [Google's list of third party vendors certified for ads](https://support.google.com/dfp_sb/answer/94149). You may visit these websites to opt out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability). Alternatively, you can opt out of some third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://aboutads.info/).
